<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:excerpt="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/excerpt/"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:wp="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/"
  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
>
<channel>

  <title>Travel Blog: Summer &#39;09</title>
  <description><p>
June 27 - Aug 30, 2009: On the road with my Honda Shadow 750, riding alongside my hubby and his BMW R1150GS. Then to England, Jersey and France. Back to Nanaimo through the USA on above-mentionned bikes. Well, this is the plan at least...</p>
</description>
  <!--<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 10:21:23 </pubDate>-->
  <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2009 01:48:30 -0400</pubDate>
  <language>en-US</language>
  <wp:wxr_version>1.2</wp:wxr_version>

  <wp:author>
    <wp:author_id></wp:author_id>
    <wp:author_login><![CDATA[ bonthorn ]]></wp:author_login>
    <wp:author_email><![CDATA[ mattbonn@gmail.com ]]></wp:author_email>
    <wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[ bonthorn ]]></wp:author_display_name>
    <wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[  ]]></wp:author_first_name>
    <wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[  ]]></wp:author_last_name>
  </wp:author>

 

  <item>
    <title>turbulent tummy</title>
    <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 17:59:07 -0400</pubDate>
    <dc:creator><![CDATA[ bonthorn ]]></dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">2_1257919119</guid>
    <description>Markham, Canada</description>

    <wp:post_date>2009-08-20 17:59:07</wp:post_date>
    <wp:post_date_gmt>2009-08-20 21:59:07</wp:post_date_gmt>
    <wp:post_name>turbulent tummy</wp:post_name>
    <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
    <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>

    <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[

<!-- ENTRY HEADER STARTS -->
<table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" align="right" width="100%">
  <tr>
    <td valign="top" align="center" padding: 20px;>
      <div style="width:50%; margin:auto; padding:10px; border:2px solid #eeeeee; text-align:center;"> turbulent tummy<br/>Markham, Canada </div>
    </td>
  </tr>
</table>
<b>Markham, Canada</b>
<br/>
<br/>
<!-- ENTRY HEADER ENDS -->

<!-- ENTRY BODY -->
We arrived in Toronto despite the tornado and lightening &#x26;amp; thunder storm. What a landing!<br> <br> Was I ever glad to be off that plane! I can't remember the last time i was ever sick but it is not pleasant.<br> <br> All i want is a bed now. Goodnight!<br> 
<br/>
<!-- ENTRY BODY ENDS -->    
<br/>

]]>
    </content:encoded>
  </item>

 

  <item>
    <title>a family affair</title>
    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2009 17:58:15 -0400</pubDate>
    <dc:creator><![CDATA[ bonthorn ]]></dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">2_1257919066</guid>
    <description>Scarborough, Canada</description>

    <wp:post_date>2009-08-21 17:58:15</wp:post_date>
    <wp:post_date_gmt>2009-08-21 21:58:15</wp:post_date_gmt>
    <wp:post_name>a family affair</wp:post_name>
    <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
    <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>

    <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[

<!-- ENTRY HEADER STARTS -->
<table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" align="right" width="100%">
  <tr>
    <td valign="top" align="center" padding: 20px;>
      <div style="width:50%; margin:auto; padding:10px; border:2px solid #eeeeee; text-align:center;"> a family affair<br/>Scarborough, Canada </div>
    </td>
  </tr>
</table>
<b>Scarborough, Canada</b>
<br/>
<br/>
<!-- ENTRY HEADER ENDS -->

<!-- ENTRY BODY -->
A family bbq with all the grandchildren there, what a treat for<br> Grandma! Being the oldest grandchild, I felt a bit old - and vertically<br> challenged, but there you have it!<br> 
<br/>
<!-- ENTRY BODY ENDS -->    
<br/>

]]>
    </content:encoded>
  </item>

 

  <item>
    <title>in the saddle again and loving it</title>
    <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2009 17:57:19 -0400</pubDate>
    <dc:creator><![CDATA[ bonthorn ]]></dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">2_1257918986</guid>
    <description>Durand, MI</description>

    <wp:post_date>2009-08-22 17:57:19</wp:post_date>
    <wp:post_date_gmt>2009-08-22 21:57:19</wp:post_date_gmt>
    <wp:post_name>in the saddle again and loving it</wp:post_name>
    <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
    <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>

    <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[

<!-- ENTRY HEADER STARTS -->
<table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" align="right" width="100%">
  <tr>
    <td valign="top" align="center" padding: 20px;>
      <div style="width:50%; margin:auto; padding:10px; border:2px solid #eeeeee; text-align:center;"> in the saddle again and loving it<br/>Durand, MI </div>
    </td>
  </tr>
</table>
<b>Durand, MI</b>
<br/>
<br/>
<!-- ENTRY HEADER ENDS -->

<!-- ENTRY BODY -->
We're heading west to go home after a fantastic summer. <br> <br> It feels so right to be back on my bike again, it's like we never parted.<br> <br> Was on the road by noon. A good, albeit wet, ride today. A bit of delay at the Sarnia/Port Huron border for Matt to renew his visa waiver form but no complaints.<br> <br> It will be interesting to compare the journey back through the US. Already i notice the incessant Golden Arches that are at every single junction. <br> <br> Aiming to be back in Nanaimo by September 1st but we'll see how things develop and how the roads are. <br> <br> This journey is to be savoured.<br> 
<br/>
<!-- ENTRY BODY ENDS -->    
<br/>

]]>
    </content:encoded>
  </item>

 

  <item>
    <title>familiar feeling</title>
    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2009 17:56:04 -0400</pubDate>
    <dc:creator><![CDATA[ bonthorn ]]></dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">2_1257918934</guid>
    <description>Madison, WI</description>

    <wp:post_date>2009-08-23 17:56:04</wp:post_date>
    <wp:post_date_gmt>2009-08-23 21:56:04</wp:post_date_gmt>
    <wp:post_name>familiar feeling</wp:post_name>
    <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
    <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>

    <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[

<!-- ENTRY HEADER STARTS -->
<table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" align="right" width="100%">
  <tr>
    <td valign="top" align="center" padding: 20px;>
      <div style="width:50%; margin:auto; padding:10px; border:2px solid #eeeeee; text-align:center;"> familiar feeling<br/>Madison, WI </div>
    </td>
  </tr>
</table>
<b>Madison, WI</b>
<br/>
<br/>
<!-- ENTRY HEADER ENDS -->

<!-- ENTRY BODY -->
We rode for 630km today .... a bit more really because we did a few detours trying to find a place for a deep-pan pizza lunch (very difficult since most places are closed on Sundays, which we didn't know - or expect!) and at around the 200 km mark on my odometer, we found<br> ourselves on the Chicago Sky route (this narrow highway 'bridge' with no shoulder) and so we had to turn off quickly to try and find any gas station or risk me running into a dry tank. We ended up detouring around some local airport in an industrial area - a very 'interesting' insight into Chicago's suburbs. But at least we found a petrol station in the end. <br> <br> Going through Chicago itself was fantastic. The skyline is beautiful, and although we got stuck in brutal traffic for over an hour (going at about 10km/hr) this will probably be the only<br> major city we actually ride through. But we were glad to be out of the traffic jam...my left hand was starting to ache from controlling the clutch at low speed. Good practice indeed! At one point we just turned off our engines and pushed our bikes along slowly.<br> <br> We've gone through Michigan, Indiana, Illinois, and now we're in Madison, Wisconsin. There aren't any 'border crossings' as such and sometimes not even a sign to tell you you're in another state. It all merges and flows into one another. All names to me before this trip, but I'm<br> slowly piecing together the gigantic puzzle of this country. I find it interesting to see all the various license plates and notice where they're coming from. The furthest so far iIve seen is Colorado and New York. No BC plates yet!<br> <br> At around 6pm (we crossed a time zone after having passed Chicago, so we gained another hour!) we stopped for dinner just before Rockford. Michigan. We shared the popular and<br> delicious Chicago beef sandwich and I have to admit i caved and ordered a huge plate of msg-filled Chinese food from 'Panda Express' :) <br> <br> We were still pretty energetic so we decided to ride for another couple of hours.... we hit a massive traffic jam about 30 kms into it and were stuck for quite a while. More clutch-control exercises for me!! There was a major car crash on the other side but traffic did eventually<br> move.... the poor people trying to get back into Chicago after a weekend must've been waiting for hours! I noticed that the standstill on that side went on for more than 10kms!<br> <br> Today our aim is to get to Sioux Falls, South Dakota. The next day we should be in Rapid<br> City (the badlands!) where we'll pass by Mount Rushmore...<br> <br> Hopefully we'll have enough time to take it slowly and meander through Yellowstone National Park, definitely something I've been looking forward to since we started.<br> <br> We're staying America's Best Value Inn and value it is. For $44 USD we get a king-size bed, free wifi, cable tv, an outdoor pool, and the breakfast - phenomenal! There are waffle makers that you can help yourself to, scrambled eggs, potatoes, sausages, cereal, bagels, pastries and American style grits! They sure do value their food here, especially in quantity!
<br/>
<!-- ENTRY BODY ENDS -->    
<br/>

]]>
    </content:encoded>
  </item>

 

  <item>
    <title>guardian angel</title>
    <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2009 17:55:04 -0400</pubDate>
    <dc:creator><![CDATA[ bonthorn ]]></dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">2_1257918875</guid>
    <description>Albert Lea, MN</description>

    <wp:post_date>2009-08-24 17:55:04</wp:post_date>
    <wp:post_date_gmt>2009-08-24 21:55:04</wp:post_date_gmt>
    <wp:post_name>guardian angel</wp:post_name>
    <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
    <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>

    <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[

<!-- ENTRY HEADER STARTS -->
<table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" align="right" width="100%">
  <tr>
    <td valign="top" align="center" padding: 20px;>
      <div style="width:50%; margin:auto; padding:10px; border:2px solid #eeeeee; text-align:center;"> guardian angel<br/>Albert Lea, MN </div>
    </td>
  </tr>
</table>
<b>Albert Lea, MN</b>
<br/>
<br/>
<!-- ENTRY HEADER ENDS -->

<!-- ENTRY BODY -->
Our first day with sunshine, even at 10am (after excellent free<br> breakfast included in our $44 room) it was baking hot but cooler as we<br> got moving. Got some good miles done, then lunch at Subway just after<br> we crossed the Mississippsiiisiiispiii River (sp?).<br> <br> Then things<br> got worse, Bonnie got a bit of turbulent tummy so she overtook me and<br> directed us off the Interstate just south of Rochester. Eventually we<br> found a gas station where she pulled up at the pump then rushed to find<br> a toilet. While she was in there I filled the bikes. <br> <br> She got<br> back, we were about to set off then I realised we were at a diesel<br> pump! Bonnie had just pulled up at the first pump so she could run to<br> the toilet and I hadn't checked what it was, we'll learn to double<br> check, but didn't we say that when we did exactly the same thing in<br> France a year ago???<br> <br> Luckily we hadn't started the engines and<br> just as we were walking the bikes to the parking lot Byron rode up on<br> his antique BMW. He is the area representative for BMW owners of<br> America and today he was our samaritan and saviour. 4 hours later both<br> tanks were drained and although he offered to put up his old tent and<br> let us sleep in his back yard we managed to get another 100kms down the<br> road and stayed the night in Albert Lea.<br> <br> Sleepy Minnesota town<br> and the lady at the motel check in desk told us not to worry about<br> vandalism and that we should park next to the white Toyota, just under<br> the streetlamp so it would be visible from the motel reception area. I<br> went outside to tell Bonnie then a man with a<br> hammer chased a woman<br> out of the hotel restaurant, she got into the white Toyota and he<br> started screaming at her and attacking the Toyota with a hammer. She<br> drove off and within seconds police cars had converged and arrested the<br> hammer man.<br> <br> Enough drama for the day, we had a sandwich and<br> salad and beer at the hotel restaurant, then to bed. Forecast of some<br> thunder showers tomorrow but as long as we get less drama than today I<br> won't be complaining!<br> <br> Matt (filling in as blogger while Bonnie rests)
<br/>
<!-- ENTRY BODY ENDS -->    
<br/>

]]>
    </content:encoded>
  </item>

 

  <item>
    <title>redeemed</title>
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2009 17:31:31 -0400</pubDate>
    <dc:creator><![CDATA[ bonthorn ]]></dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">2_1257917461</guid>
    <description>Wall, SD</description>

    <wp:post_date>2009-08-25 17:31:31</wp:post_date>
    <wp:post_date_gmt>2009-08-25 21:31:31</wp:post_date_gmt>
    <wp:post_name>redeemed</wp:post_name>
    <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
    <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>

    <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[

<!-- ENTRY HEADER STARTS -->
<table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" align="right" width="100%">
  <tr>
    <td valign="top" align="center" padding: 20px;>
      <div style="width:50%; margin:auto; padding:10px; border:2px solid #eeeeee; text-align:center;"> redeemed<br/>Wall, SD </div>
    </td>
  </tr>
</table>
<b>Wall, SD</b>
<br/>
<br/>
<!-- ENTRY HEADER ENDS -->

<!-- ENTRY BODY -->
Today:<br> -started off with some intense spurts of rain<br> -sunshine and big open skies followed<br> -miles and miles of corn fields dotted with wind turbines<br> -saw a plane dusting sunflower fields, very very cool<br> -long straight empty roads, wishing for twisty roads<br> -passed many billboards.. getting sick of them but can't help reading them! <br> -Many advertise the towns and attractions ahead. If you've passed the exit<br> junction, the next billboard will scream "STOP! You've just missed<br> XXXXX, turn off at next exit"<br> -Many messages of faith and Christianity. Ie: "There are many ways to go to hell but only one way to heaven - Jesus"<br> -Into the Badlands National Park, Matt tipped his bike over at entrance while<br> trying to read the signs.... adrenalin pumping, he yanks the bike<br> upright just as i ran over. No visible damage.<br> -Incredible scenery at Badlands<br> -the twisty roads were excellent!!<br> -Had yummy 'Indian Taco' at local family diner in Wall. It's fried dough<br> bread (bannock) topped with refried beans, ground beef, salad and<br> cheese. <br> <br> Summary:<br> Successful riding day! 771 kms exact! Redeemed ourselves after yesterday's incident. On schedule once more.<br> 
<br/>
<!-- ENTRY BODY ENDS -->    
<br/>

]]>
    </content:encoded>
  </item>

 

  <item>
    <title>the perfect day</title>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 17:54:06 -0400</pubDate>
    <dc:creator><![CDATA[ bonthorn ]]></dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">2_1257918817</guid>
    <description>Ten Sleep, WY</description>

    <wp:post_date>2009-08-26 17:54:06</wp:post_date>
    <wp:post_date_gmt>2009-08-26 21:54:06</wp:post_date_gmt>
    <wp:post_name>the perfect day</wp:post_name>
    <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
    <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>

    <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[

<!-- ENTRY HEADER STARTS -->
<table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" align="right" width="100%">
  <tr>
    <td valign="top" align="center" padding: 20px;>
      <div style="width:50%; margin:auto; padding:10px; border:2px solid #eeeeee; text-align:center;"> the perfect day<br/>Ten Sleep, WY </div>
    </td>
  </tr>
</table>
<b>Ten Sleep, WY</b>
<br/>
<br/>
<!-- ENTRY HEADER ENDS -->

<!-- ENTRY BODY -->
627 km of blissful riding. Probably the most enjoyable riding day I've ever had in my short riding career. <br> <br> We've gone through some interesting and unique town names, many derived from<br> the First Nations who were here first and created legends about the<br> land. Some names include: Kalamazoo,....and others i will post later<br> <br> After riding on the I-90 for some time now, we decided to take a side route<br> to get to Yellowstone National Park. By chance, we turned west after<br> Buffalo and the scenery just got more and more dramatic. It was<br> absolutely stunning, no other words to describe it. You know how some<br> things can look/hear/taste/feel so incredible that you would actually<br> tear up? Well, this was one of those moments.<br> <br> I'm going to cheat and copy/paste what the Ten Sleep website has wrote about on how its name was derived:<br> <br> "Nestled in the base of the Big Horn Mountains in the Nowood Valley, 26 miles<br> east of Worland on US Highway 16, Ten Sleep long ago staked its claim<br> to a share of Wyoming&#8217;s and Washakie County&#8217;s colored history. Ten<br> Sleep received its name because of the method of measuring<br> distance that was used by Indians at one time.<br> <br> There was once a large Sioux Indian camp on the banks of the Platte River,<br> and there was another large Indian camp on the Clark's Fork River to<br> the North, near present-day Bridger, Montana. These camps<br> were important to Indians and settlers due to the trails leading to <br> <br> and from them in all directions across the West. According to the<br> reckoning of the Indians, it was twenty "sleeps," or nights, between<br> the two camps. <br> <br> It took ten "sleeps" to get halfway between them. This became the<br> location of the present town of Ten Sleep." <br> <br> With a population of 350 (estimated) it is a sleepy little Western town but<br> full of natural glory and splendor. And with delicious oven-baked pizza<br> too in the town's only pizzeria!<br> 
<br/>
<!-- ENTRY BODY ENDS -->    
<br/>

]]>
    </content:encoded>
  </item>

 

  <item>
    <title>wooooosh!!!!!!!</title>
    <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2009 17:52:07 -0400</pubDate>
    <dc:creator><![CDATA[ bonthorn ]]></dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">2_1257918696</guid>
    <description>West Yellowstone, MT</description>

    <wp:post_date>2009-08-27 17:52:07</wp:post_date>
    <wp:post_date_gmt>2009-08-27 21:52:07</wp:post_date_gmt>
    <wp:post_name>wooooosh!!!!!!!</wp:post_name>
    <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
    <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>

    <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[

<!-- ENTRY HEADER STARTS -->
<table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" align="right" width="100%">
  <tr>
    <td valign="top" align="center" padding: 20px;>
      <div style="width:50%; margin:auto; padding:10px; border:2px solid #eeeeee; text-align:center;"> wooooosh!!!!!!!<br/>West Yellowstone, MT </div>
    </td>
  </tr>
</table>
<b>West Yellowstone, MT</b>
<br/>
<br/>
<!-- ENTRY HEADER ENDS -->

<!-- ENTRY BODY -->
Old Faithful didn't disappoint. <br> <br> Saw a beautiful bison at sunset. <br> <br> Good riding but the traffic made it more exhausting than necessary. Apparently Yellowstone National Park gets 30,000+ visitors PER DAY!<br> <br> More to come later... just wanted to post pics now while i have high-speed connection.
<br/>
<!-- ENTRY BODY ENDS -->    
<br/>

]]>
    </content:encoded>
  </item>

 

  <item>
    <title>a must see!</title>
    <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2009 17:53:18 -0400</pubDate>
    <dc:creator><![CDATA[ bonthorn ]]></dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">2_1257918769</guid>
    <description>Columbia Falls, MT</description>

    <wp:post_date>2009-08-28 17:53:18</wp:post_date>
    <wp:post_date_gmt>2009-08-28 21:53:18</wp:post_date_gmt>
    <wp:post_name>a must see!</wp:post_name>
    <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
    <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>

    <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[

<!-- ENTRY HEADER STARTS -->
<table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" align="right" width="100%">
  <tr>
    <td valign="top" align="center" padding: 20px;>
      <div style="width:50%; margin:auto; padding:10px; border:2px solid #eeeeee; text-align:center;"> a must see!<br/>Columbia Falls, MT </div>
    </td>
  </tr>
</table>
<b>Columbia Falls, MT</b>
<br/>
<br/>
<!-- ENTRY HEADER ENDS -->

<!-- ENTRY BODY -->
Glacier National Park is fantastic. The highway, named "Into The Sun Highway" (exactly what we were doing!), hugs the mountainside, dips into valleys and brings you up through glorious passes. It's like a 50 km scenic roller coaster ride. Wheeeee!
<br/>
<!-- ENTRY BODY ENDS -->    
<br/>

]]>
    </content:encoded>
  </item>

 

  <item>
    <title>Canadian homecoming</title>
    <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2009 17:08:24 -0400</pubDate>
    <dc:creator><![CDATA[ bonthorn ]]></dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">2_1257916075</guid>
    <description>Grand Forks, Canada</description>

    <wp:post_date>2009-08-29 17:08:24</wp:post_date>
    <wp:post_date_gmt>2009-08-29 21:08:24</wp:post_date_gmt>
    <wp:post_name>Canadian homecoming</wp:post_name>
    <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
    <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>

    <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[

<!-- ENTRY HEADER STARTS -->
<table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" align="right" width="100%">
  <tr>
    <td valign="top" align="center" padding: 20px;>
      <div style="width:50%; margin:auto; padding:10px; border:2px solid #eeeeee; text-align:center;"> Canadian homecoming<br/>Grand Forks, Canada </div>
    </td>
  </tr>
</table>
<b>Grand Forks, Canada</b>
<br/>
<br/>
<!-- ENTRY HEADER ENDS -->

<!-- ENTRY BODY -->
Another beautiful ride in the Rockies. Everything is just so green! <br> <br> And fantastic twisty roads going up and down and around mountain bends...<br> there were a few times where my poor bike just couldn't catch up to<br> Matt's, throttle open and all! Going around a sharp right hand corner<br> at one point my right foot peg skimmed the ground.. it shook me up a<br> bit but no damage done.<br> <br> We crossed back into Canada from the Idaho border. It feels good to be back on Canadian soil. <br> <br> We immediately stopped at a local cafe in Creston for a good smoothie and<br> homemade chilli. For some reason, I'm feeling much safer and relaxed<br> being back in BC.<br> <br> We checked into this fantastic motel in quaint Grand Forks and then walked next door for a delicious Russian meal. The borscht and perogies were like something i've never tasted before! What a welcome change from Subway lunches and burgers and fries!<br> <br> 523 km to go until home! Can't wait to be riding up to our apartment, I've<br> imagined this for so long. Last stretch, we'll be sure to make it safe.<br> 
<br/>
<!-- ENTRY BODY ENDS -->    
<br/>

]]>
    </content:encoded>
  </item>

 

  <item>
    <title>the green green grass of home</title>
    <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2009 17:05:10 -0400</pubDate>
    <dc:creator><![CDATA[ bonthorn ]]></dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">2_1253349305</guid>
    <description>Nanaimo, Canada</description>

    <wp:post_date>2009-08-30 17:05:10</wp:post_date>
    <wp:post_date_gmt>2009-08-30 21:05:10</wp:post_date_gmt>
    <wp:post_name>the green green grass of home</wp:post_name>
    <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
    <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>

    <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[

<!-- ENTRY HEADER STARTS -->
<table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" align="right" width="100%">
  <tr>
    <td valign="top" align="center" padding: 20px;>
      <div style="width:50%; margin:auto; padding:10px; border:2px solid #eeeeee; text-align:center;"> the green green grass of home<br/>Nanaimo, Canada </div>
    </td>
  </tr>
</table>
<b>Nanaimo, Canada</b>
<br/>
<br/>
<!-- ENTRY HEADER ENDS -->

<!-- ENTRY BODY -->
We made it on the ferry - with seconds to spare! But for some reason,<br> just based on how everything worked out on this trip, we both knew we<br> would make the ferry, even when all the factors seemed stacked against<br> us. And even if we didn&#8217;t, the next one was only 2 hours later. <br> But we made it, and we are excited to be home in a couple of hours!<br> <br> Some<br> might look at my Honda Shadow 750 and think it was only a piece of<br> complicated machinery put together in a factory. But I have come to<br> love and care for this bike like it were an extension of myself. And so<br> it's only right that I give it the proper thanks it deserves....<br> <br> <br> Dear Beloved Bike,<br> <br> Our<br> journey is coming to an end. I am sitting here eating sushi on the<br> ferry deck while you&#8217;re down below on the vehicle deck. We are minutes<br> away from Nanaimo. <br> <br> It has been a tremendous journey<br> this summer, seeing parts of Canada and the USA, all on your reliable<br> two wheels. You never let me down and kept me safe every second of the<br> way, during the torrential downpours, the gravel tracks, the miles of<br> construction and detours, the starless nights, the thick forest roads<br> and the great open plains. You gave every ounce of energy to this<br> journey, you responded to every request of mine and you never gave up.<br> <br> I&#8217;m<br> sorry about the diesel in your tank; that incident taught us to be more<br> vigilant when selecting your &#8216;drink of choice&#8217;. I&#8217;m just glad you<br> weren&#8217;t further damaged.<br> <br> I was most proud when my family got to<br> see (and ride!) you for the first time. I also enjoyed all the random<br> conversations that were started in various gas stations around the<br> continent, all because of you!<br> <br> It will probably be a<br> while before we embark on another long-distance road trip. But we&#8217;ll<br> still cruise around town and on do some island daytrips. There&#8217;s no way<br> I want to ever stop riding; you have given me the experience and the<br> memories that have made me a lifelong rider. And a safe one too. What<br> more could I ask for?<br> <br> Thank you for this golden opportunity to have this roadtrip of a lifetime. Those 10529.5 kms won't be forgotten anytime soon!<br> <br> <br> Bon xoxo<br> 
<br/>
<!-- ENTRY BODY ENDS -->    
<br/>

]]>
    </content:encoded>
  </item>



</channel>
</rss>